<Document>
  # Server Rules
  Nebulous Stories exists to foster high quality roleplay in all capacities. Here, players may create characters that engage in collaborative roleplay and do cool things. These characters have few rules binding their freedom, bar that they do engage in quality roleplay. We support a community of players who share similar desires: to tell good stories over achieve mechanical wins. Above all else, we hold that respect is key.
  \nDue to the nature of HRP and this server, players are given the freedom to discuss mature and potentially sensitive topics. If you are uncomfortable with such content, we recommend that you do not play.


  [color=#ff0000]By connecting to Nebulous Stories you confirm you are 18 years old or older. If you are suspected of being under 18 you will be permanently removed.[/color]

  All rules apply at all times unless specified otherwise by an admin.

  [deadspace][Yes this is the only way I know how to do this]

  \n[head=3][color=#ff3636]1.0 - Zero Tolerance Policies[/color][/head]
  \n[color=#e6e6e6]Core policies and rules that we provide no or extremely low amounts of leeway and tolerance for.[/color]

  - [textlink="1.1 Admins reserve the right to disregard any and all rules should they deem it to be in the interest of the current round, server, or community." link="Rule1.1"]
  - [textlink="1.2 This is an English only server, you should be using it as your primary method of communication." link="Rule1.2"]
  - [textlink="1.3 Do not communicate in-round information to other people." link="Rule1.3"]
  - [textlink="1.4 No discrimination or bigotry." link="Rule1.4"]
  - [textlink="1.5 Respect others' consent choices." link="Rule1.5"]
  - [textlink="1.6 Do not ignore, intentionally disconnect from, or react with hostility in the ahelp." link="Rule1.6"]
  - [textlink="1.7 Do not abuse exploits or bugs." link="Rule1.7"]

  \n[head=3][color=#3bff72]2.0 - General Rules[/color][/head]
  \n[color=#e6e6e6]General rules and common practice. The "bare-minimum" expectations that you should be following.[/color]

  - [textlink="2.1 Have in-round reason, rationale, and roleplay for your character's actions." link="Rule2.1"]
  - [textlink="2.2 Do not meta-friend or meta-grudge." link="Rule2.2"]
  - [textlink="2.3 Speak and act like a believable person." link="Rule2.3"]
  - [textlink="2.4 As a non antagonist, do not commit major crimes without admin approval." link="Rule2.4"]
  - [textlink="2.5 Keep your damage proportional to your objectives." link="Rule2.5"]

  \n[head=3][color=#59ffe1]3.0 - Roleplay Expectations[/color][/head]
  \n[color=#e6e6e6]Expectations and policies centered around roleplay.[/color]

  - [textlink="3.1 Your character is a separate entity from you, the player." link="Rule3.1"]
  - [textlink="3.2 Do not intentionally prepare items “just in case”." link="Rule3.2"]
  - [textlink="3.3 Do not overcrowd departmental RP situations." link="Rule3.3"]
  - [textlink="3.4 Do not seek out to kill or detain unrelated threats." link="Rule3.4"]
  - [textlink="3.5 Follow the new life rule." link="Rule3.5"]
  - [textlink="3.6 Stay within your job, reasonable knowledge, and abilities." link="Rule3.6"]
  - [textlink="3.7 Command and security are expected to be competent and lawful." link="Rule3.7"]
</Document>
